# **Doung Kolbondith**

# **Frontend Developer**

### **Doung Kolbondith**

No:468, Sangkat Steung Meanchey, Khan Meanchey, Kingdom of Cambodia

+85512624966 kolbondith@gmail.com

### **Profile**

I am an ambitious and creative person who is very enthusiastic about everything related to content creator. I am currently a scholar and a sophomore in Kirirom Institute of Technology majoring in Software Engineering. I have experience working on network maintenance and webapp development.

### **Experience**

## **DynamiXD** / Maintenance Worker

January 2019 - April 2020

Maintain the network in Kiirirom. I was very enthusiastic about maintaining the network and handling some server in data center.

I and my team have made a various achievement such as:

- Install the light backup in every dorm
- Designed the network structure in new Borey
- Install camera in new area

# Flib / Frontend Developer

January 2021 - Octoberl 2022

I was passionate about doing a project with my team member.my role was to maintain the project to run smoothly, add new features and fix bugs.

#### **Education**

### **Bak Touk Primary School**

October 2006 - November 2012

### **Cheasim Samaki High School**

November 2012 - November 2018

#### **Kirirom Institude Of Technology**

November 2018 - Present